Coream Kang

Web Developer/Designer at Atlassian

Summary

Accomplished web developer and graphic artist with over ten years of experience developing and implementing interactive applications while helping small, successful start-up companies execute plans to meet their goals. Works best on teams that strive to innovate using technology, new media and creative.

Specialties: XHTML / CSS Development, Corporate Identity Development, Graphic Design, User Interface Implementation

Experience

Senior Web Developer at Atlassian

November 2010 - Present

Freelance Web Developer/Designer

June 2008 - Present

Accomplished web developer and graphic artist with over ten years of experience developing and implementing interactive applications while helping small, successful start-up companies execute plans to meet their goals. Works best on teams that strive to innovate using technology, new media and creative.

Front-End Web Developer at Arena Solutions

July 2009 - August 2010 (1 year 1 month)

CMS Developer at Draftfcb

2010 - 2010 (less than a year)

Web Specialist

2007 - 2010 (3 years)

Front-End Web Developer

2009 - 2009 (less than a year)

Web Developer/UI Designer

December 1999 - June 2008 (8 years 6 months)

Quality Rater at Google

March 2006 - April 2008 (2 years 1 month)

Optimizing the search results for Korean language search

Front-End Web Developer

2008 - 2008 (less than a year)

Web Producer

2000 - 2000 (less than a year)

Web Developer at WebMD

1999 - 1999 (less than a year)

Education

California State University-Long Beach

BA, Graphic Design, 1996 - 1998

Coream Kang

Web Developer/Designer at Atlassian



Contact Coream on LinkedIn